Well, there is the following
There is the "good soul" for example
And what the "good soul" does is act in the world
In world prospects
To generate the truth of the world
And the Judeo-Christian proposal is
Is that if you encounter the possibilities of the world
In good faith
Using the truth
Sincere communication
When, then, what results from that is good
This was repeated in Genesis
When God used the word
And the universe was created out of possibility
And every time he does that he says:
"And it was good."
So I think it's very interesting
There's a suggestion out there, and the suggestion is
If you face potential with truth,
The world you create is already going to be good
Well this one
This is an interesting idea, if true
If it is real, then it is the greatest truth in existence